We're running low on resumes.
瑞秋,履歷表已用完了
You want a job with Popular Mechanics?
你真想到「大眾技工」上班嗎?
If you're gonna work for mechanics, those are the ones.
如果你真想為技工工作 那兒倒兒可試試
Guys,I'm going for anything here. I can't be a waitress anymore.
各位,我什麼都得試試 我不能再當服務生了
I'm sick of the lousy tips. I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me."
我是說真的我已厭倦微薄小費 我已厭倦別人對我說「麻煩一下」
-Paper cut! Paper cut! -Here.
-裁紙刀!裁紙刀! -這裡
Grapefruit juice! Grapefruit juice!
柚子汁!柚子汁!
Okay,we're almost done. Only 20 more to go.
差不多搞定了.只剩20份了
-Rach,did you proofread these? -Yeah. Why?
-瑞秋,這些你已校對過? -對,有問題嗎?
Nothing. I'm sure they'll be impressed with your "compuper" skills.
沒事,他們對你的「墊腦」技巧一定會印象深刻的
Oh,my God! Do you think it's on all of them?
糟了,每一份上面都這樣嗎?
No,I'm sure the Xerox machine caught a few.
沒有,影印機弄掉一些了
The One With the Poker
六人行 第1季 第18集 玩撲克
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
They call this a love seat but I'm not feeling anything special towards you.
他們把這裡叫做情侶座. 可是和你對面一點感覺都沒有
-Hey,guys. -Hey.
-嗨,小伙子們 -嗨
Hi,ladies.
嗨,小姐們
Can I get you anything? Did you bring the mail?
需要什麼嗎?信件帶來了沒?
-Lots of responses. -Really? Sure,we have scones left!
-很多回復 -當然?我們這兒當然有烤餅
Read them.
快念給我聽
"Dear Miss Greene: Thank you for your inquiry. However"
親愛的格林小姐感謝您的詢問,然而…
-We have apple cinnamon -"Dear Ms. Greene...." Yeah,yeah! No.
-我們有蘋果肉桂…-親愛的格林小姐…好，好，不行.
-What? -Your Visa bill is huge!
-怎麼了?-你的開銷不小呀
Give me that.
給我
Linda's great. Why won't you go out with her?
我真不敢相信 琳達那麼好你為何不再和她約會?
-I don't know. -ls this about her...
-我也不知道 -是因為她說了
... "The Flintstones could have really happened" thing?
石頭族真有可能發生?
It's not just that. I want someone who does something for me...
不只是因為那樣 因為我要一個能讓我有感覺
...who gets my heart pounding.
能讓我心跳加速
Who makes me....
讓我…
Little playthings with yarn?
感情經驗豐富的女人
What?
什麼?
Could you want her more?
你不是渴望著她?
Who?
誰?
Dee,the sarcastic sister from What's Happening!!.
明蒂,《發生何事》中 那個尖酸刻薄的女孩
Look,I'm totally over her.
我早就忘了她,行嗎?
-Hi! -Coffee?
-好啊! -咖啡?
-No,we're fine. -Okay.
-我們很好 -好的
-Shut up! -We're not saying anything.
-閉嘴! -我們什麼都沒說
-What? -Joey cried last night.
-什麼? -昨晚喬伊哭了
-Thank you. -We were playing poker
-謝謝 -我們正在玩撲克牌
There was chocolate on the three. It looked like an eight.
三點上有巧克力看起來像是八點
You should have seen him. "Read them and weep!"
可惜你沒看到 他說「準備痛哭流涕吧」
And then he did.
結果哭的是他
Now,how come you guys have never played poker with us?
你們怎麼沒和我們玩過撲克牌?
Yeah,what is that? Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
對,為什麼? 好像這是有性別歧視的男人的專利
-It's poker,so only guys can play? -No. Women can play.
-這是撲克,只有男人才玩?  -才怪,女生也歡迎加人
Then,what is it? Some kind of,like, some kind of,you know
那麼為什麼…這樣的一些,為什麼
All right,what is it?
到底為什麼?
There are just no women in our game.
只是剛好女生沒加入罷了
We just don't know any women who know how to play poker.
對,我們剛好找不到會玩的女生
That is a lame excuse. It's a typical guy response.
拜託,這個借口真爛 男生都是這種反應
Do you know how to play?
請問你們誰會玩撲克牌?
No.
不會
-But you could teach us. -No.
-你們可以教我 -不要
Okay,so now we draw cards.
現在開始抽牌
So I wouldn't need any. I have a straight.
我不需要換牌對吧? 因為我一把順
-Oh,good for you! -Congratulations!
-對你來說不錯! -恭喜了!
-Pheebs,how many do you want? -I just need two.
-菲比,你要幾張? -我需要兩張
The 10 of spades and the 6 of clubs.
黑桃十和梅花六
-No,you can't -I have the 10 of spades! Here.
-不,你不能那樣做 -等等,我有你要的黑桃
Thanks!
謝謝!
-No,you can't do that. -Don't need them. I'm going for fours.
-不…不能那樣 -不…可以,我不需要.我要四張同點
Oh,you're
哦,你們
You're going for fours. Chandler,could you? Thanks,man.
我要四張同點.錢德, 你有嗎?謝謝,小伙
Here we go.
開始吧
We've got salmon roulettes and crudites.
我們有鮭魚樂透和水果盤
What are you doing?
摩妮卡,你在幹什麼?
In poker,there's no food with more than one syllable.
撲克裡面,食物的名稱不能超過一個音節
It's got to be like chips or dip or pretz
洋芋片,沙司,椒鹽卷…
I hope you'll let it slide just this once. I was all out of "pretz."
我希望你能只卷這一次
Now the dealer
現在開始發牌
We got it. Let's play for real. High stakes. Big bucks!
知道了.開始玩真的吧.高賭資,大筆錢
You sure? Phoebe just threw away two jacks because they didn't look happy.
你當真?菲比剛丟出十一點(傑克) 因為他們好像不開心
But I'm ready. So just deal.
我準備好了,發牌
Okay,last-minute lesson! Joey....
各位,最後通知!喬伊有
Three.
三點
Eight.
八點
Eight. Three. All right,very good.
八點,三點,好的,不錯
Damn it,damn it,damn it!
該死,該死,該死!
Joey had two fives showing, so for you to raise was
喬伊面上又一對5,該你們叫牌
Yes?
好的?
Downright gutsy.
明顯而且大膽
-I see,so you were lying. -About what?
-我明白,就是騙 -騙什麼?
-About how good your cards were. -I was bluffing.
-騙你們牌有多好 -我在唬你們
And what is bluffing?
什麼是唬?
Is it not another word for lying?
不就是騙的同義字嗎?
Sorry to break up this party,but I've got to go fax resumes before work.
抱歉,我不能再玩了 我在明天工作前得打好履歷表
-We've got to settle. -Settle what?
-瑞秋,我們得算帳(定居) -什麼定居?
The Jamestown colony of Virginia.
在維吉尼亞的詹姆斯城殖民地
See,King George is giving us the land....
喬治王把土地給我所以…
-The game,Rachel. You owe us money. -Right.
-瑞秋,是賭局,你欠我們錢 -哦,好
It's their first time. Let's forget about the money.
你們知道嗎?這是她們的第一次 別和她們計較錢了
Hell,no. We'll pay!
不好,我們會付錢的
Monica,I had another answer all ready.
摩妮卡,我有另一個答案了
And you know what? We want a rematch.
知道嗎?我們要再來一次
That's fine with me. Could use some money.
不錯,我有錢花了
-You're enjoying this,aren't you? -Well,yeah,I am.
-你很享受這個,是不是 -我想是的
So you get your ya-yas by taking money from your friends.
這麼說你們的組閤家俱 都用朋友的錢買來的
Yes,and I get my ya-yas from KEA.
沒錯,而且我是在「宜家家俱」買的
You have to put them together yourself,but they cost less.
自己得動手裝,便宜許多
Look,this is poker. I play to win.
瑞秋,這是撲克牌,玩就是要贏
For me to win, others have to lose.
為使我能賺錢別人就得輸
If you're gonna play, don't expect me to be nice.
如果想和我玩牌就別指望我手下留情
Because once those cards are dealt....
因為牌一發出
Yeah?
然後呢?
I'm not a nice guy.
我就六親不認
All right,let's eat.
各位,吃吧
Did you get that from the "I Love Rachel Pizzeria"?
這是從「我愛瑞秋匹薩屋」買的嗎?
-You still on that? -What was with that Black Bart speech?
-你們還在取笑我? -別這樣嘛,為何學起黑道
"When I play poker, I'm not a nice guy."
玩起牌來我六親不認
You're way off.
你扯太遠了
No,I don't think so, because I think you love her!
我可不這麼認為 因為我認為你愛她
No. I might have had feelings for her at one time. Not anymore.
不,或許我曾過她有意思 愛意早已消失
I just
我只是
Marcel! Where are you going with that disk?
馬修!你想把CD片怎麼了?
You are not putting that on again.
不能再放上去,馬修
If you press that button, you are in very big trouble.
如果你們再鬧,你可真的有大麻煩了
You believe what a jerk Ross was being?
你知道羅斯那混蛋有多爛嗎?
-Yeah,I know. -He can get really competitive.
-我懂 -他的好勝心最強了
What?
什麼?
"Hello,kettle? This is Monica. You're black!"
凱蒂,我是摩妮卡,你是黑人
Please!
拜託
I'm not as bad as Ross.
我沒像羅斯那麼爛
I beg to differ. The Pictionary incident?
我抗議,「字典」事件呢?
That wasn't an incident.
我不是故意的
I was gesturing and the plate slipped out of my hand.
我在做手勢時盤子不慎滑落
-I got an interview! -You're kidding! Where?
-他們叫我去面談了! -你在開玩笑吧?哪兒?
Saks Fifth Avenue.
第五大道薩克斯
Oh,Rachel!
哦,瑞秋
It's like the mother ship is calling you home.
這就像是母船叫你歸隊
-What's the job? -Assistant buyer.
-是什麼工作? -採購助理
I would be shopping!
我要用購物…
For a living!
來謀生了
That's Aunt lris. She's been playing poker since she was 5.
她叫艾莉絲姑姑 她從五歲起便開始玩牌
You've got to listen to every word she says.
她說的每字我們都得牢記在心
-ls Tony Randall dead? -I don't think so.
-東尼藍道死了? -我看不是
-He may be now. I hit him with my car. -My God,really?
-現在可能已死因為我開車撞到他了 -天啊…真的?
No,that's bluffing. Lesson number one.
不,唬你們的,第一課
Let me tell you something. Everything you hear at a poker game is pure crap!
告訴你們玩牌聽到的每個字都是狗屁
-Nice earrings. -Thank you.
-不錯的耳環 -謝…
-Girls,sit down. -Aunt lris,this is Phoebe and Rachel.
-坐吧,各位 -艾莉絲姑姑,這位是菲比,她叫瑞秋
Listen,I'm parked at a meter. Let's do it. Okay?
我的車停在計時器前,開始吧
We'll start with five-card draw.
我們從抽五張牌開始
Then we'll go into the studs and the hold 'ems. I talked to Cousin Nathan.
然後我們開始看牌並且持牌. 我跟南希堂兄說
Don't touch the cards when somebody is dealing.
發牌的時候不要碰牌
How is Nathan?
南希怎麼樣?
Now he thinks he's a man in a woman's body.
他現在以為他是一個在女人身體裡的男人
Don't you mean a woman in a man's body?
你是說一個女人在男人的身體裡?
It should be so simple.
這很簡單是吧
Ross,could we please listen to anything else?
羅斯,我們能聽點別的嗎?
All right.
好吧
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
我今晚可要倒大楣了
Hi. Guys,guess what?
嗨,夥計們,猜猜看?
The fifth dentist caved,and now they're all recommending Trident?
第五位牙醫投奔他們,推薦「三叉戟」?
No,the interview!
不,是面談
Unbelievable! She absolutely loved me.
簡直無法相信!她喜歡我
We talked for over two hours. We've the same taste in clothes.
我們談了兩個半小時 我們對服飾的品味一致
And I went to camp with her cousin.
我從前還和她的表妹一起去過夏令營
-The job is perfect! I can do this. -That's great!
-這工作簡直是太棒了,我可以勝任 -太好了…
-Then she told a funny story. -Great,tell us and we'll laugh.
-然後她告訴我最好笑的事 -很好,你講時我們一定會笑
Let's play poker!
玩牌吧
Listen,we talked about it and if you don't wanna play,it's okay.
各位聽好,我們談過此事 如果你想不玩我們完全瞭解
Yes,we can play some other game. Like Pictionary?
對,我們可以玩別的像「字典」之類的
Very funny.
真好笑
-But we'd like to try poker again. -Yes,I think we should.
-我們想再給撲克牌一次機會 -我想是的
-Do you want me to shuffle those? -That's okay,I'm gonna give it a go.
-瑞秋,需要我來洗牌嗎? -不用了,我想自己試試
So Pheebs owes $7. 50. Monica owes $10.00.
菲比欠7塊5,摩妮卡欠10塊
And Rachel,you owe 1 5 big ones!
瑞秋,你欠15塊!
Thanks for teaching us Cross-Eyed Mary. We gotta play that other way.
謝謝教我們「斜眼瑪麗」 我們該用另一種方式玩了
All right,here's my $7.50. But this money is cursed.
這是我的7塊5,不過這錢已受到詛咒
-What? -I cursed it!
-什麼? -我已對它下咒!
Now bad things will happen to the spender.
花這些錢的人會倒大楣
I'll take it. Bad things happen to me anyway.
無所謂,我接受.我反正夠楣的了
This way,I can split them up with a movie.
這樣我才能看場電影喘口氣
So that just leaves the big Greene poker machine,who owes 1 5.
才剛離開綠色撲克牌機,誰就欠了15塊
Could you be any smugger?
你能不能不打劫呢?
Let's see. Rach,I'm opening up a new art gallery...
讓我看看.瑞秋,我準備開一個畫廊
...and I could sure use the portraits of Lincoln and Hamilton.
我肯定可以用林肯和漢密爾頓的肖像
It's so typical. "I'm a man! I have a penis!
男生都這副德行 我是男人我有大傢伙
I have to win money to exert my power over women!"
我得贏錢增加力量以征服女人
This isn't over.
知道嗎?還沒結束
We'll play you again. We'll win. You'll lose.
我們會再找你們玩 而且我們會贏你們會輸
You'll beg. We'll laugh.
你們會祈求,我們會大笑
We'll take every last dime you have. And you'll hate yourselves forever!
我們會贏走你們的每一分錢 你們會永遠恨死自己
Kind of stepped on my point there,Mon.
我們的意見一致,摩妮卡
I can't believe you lost! How much did they take?
我無法相信你輸了!有多少?
Like 30 bucks.
差不多30塊
-I'll give you that money back. -Really?
-我會把錢退回去的 -真的嗎?
No,I'm bluffing! You guys haven't learned crap!
不,我在唬你!你們還沒有學偷雞!
-Hand me the cards! -Can l?
-把牌遞給我! -我來行嗎?
Yes!
是的!
Wanna give us your money now? We can skip the formality of really playing.
現在可以交出錢來嗎? 如此我們就不必正式玩了
No,that's fine. We'll see who has the last laugh,monkey boy.
不,我倒要看看誰笑到最後,猴子男
Done with chitchat? Ready for serious poker?
聊完了沒?可以開始玩真的沒?
You guys,look! The one-eyed jack follows me wherever I go.
你們看,獨眼傑克到處跟蹤我
Right. Serious poker.
好,玩真的
-Mon,got any more of those salmon? -You want to eat or play poker?
-摩尼卡,你還有三文魚嗎? -你到底是吃東西還是玩牌?
-Where are you going? -To the bathroom.
-你要上哪兒去? -浴室
Want to go to the bathroom or play poker?
你想上廁所還是玩牌?
Go to the bathroom.
我想上廁所
-Well,I'm gonna order a pizza. -No!
-好吧,我去訂此薩 -不
I'm waiting to hear from that job. The store closes at 9:00. Eat then.
我仍等著工作的電話通知 他們的店在9點關門那時候再吃吧
That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac to hold me over.
行,我含薄荷糖提神
All right. Cincinnati. No blinds. Everybody,ante.
未見牌不得下注,下注吧
Yes!
下…
Or no.
不下
-All right! Your money's mine,Greene. -Your fly's open,Geller.
-你的錢是我的了,菜鳥 -你的拉鏈沒拉上,蓋勒
You know what I just realized? Joker is poker with a "J"!
我剛剛才瞭解到,十一點上有個J
Coincidence?
真巧?
That's jo-incidence with a "C"!
那是J碰巧和一個C在一起
-Phoebe? -Yeah,I'm out.
-菲比? -我不跟了
-I'm in. -Me too.
-我跟 -我也跟
Me too. What do you got?
我也跟,你拿什麼牌?
You better hop out of the shower, because I got a flush.
你最好逃出浴室 因為我拿五張同花(沖馬桶)
Well,well,well!
好的,好的,好的!
Hop back in,bucko, because I got four sixes!
回來吧,小子,因為我拿了四張六
I got four sixes! I won! I actually won! Oh,my God!
我有四張六!我贏了… 我真的贏了,天哪
You know what? I'll make a little Ross pile.
你們知道嗎?我要把小羅斯堆起來
Look!
看!
I think that one was Ross'. And I think that one was Ross'.
我想這是羅斯的 那個也是羅斯的
Well,I have got your money And you'll never see it
我賺到你的錢,你再無法見到它
And your fly's still open
你的拉鏈依然沒拉上
I made you look
我讓你低頭看了
-I'm in. -I couldn't be in-er.
-我跟 -我不能跟
Monica,in or out?
摩妮卡,跟還不跟?
I hate this game!
我討厭玩牌
Joey,your bet.
喬依,你呢?
I fold like a hooker who got hit in the stomach...
我像是被滿臉傷痕的胖子
... by a fat guy with sores on his face.
撞到肚子的二流妓女
I'm out.
我不跟
-Ross? -I'm very in.
-羅斯? -我跟
-Chandler? -Couldn't be more out.
-錢德? -不跟
Me too. Rachel?
我也一樣,瑞秋?
I will see you and I'll raise you. Do you wanna waste another buck?
我不但跟而且還要加注 如何?還想再浪費錢嗎?
No,not this time. What did you have?
這一回不會.快嘛,給我看
-I'm not telling. -Show them.
-我不會說的 -給我看
-No. -Show them!
-不 -給我看
-Get your hands out of there! -I've had dates like this.
-把你的手從那裡拿開! -我有同樣的約會經驗
Boy,you really can't stand to lose,can you?
天啊,你真是輸不起的傢伙
Your whole face is getting red. Veins popping out of your temple!
你的臉漲得好紅 太陽穴的小血管都浮出來了
Plus,that shirt doesn't really match those pants.
而且衣褲並不相稱
-I'm not losing. -You're definitely losing.
-第一,我沒輸 -別再談輸了,快發牌吧你輸定了
Hello. Rachel Greene.
瑞秋格林
Excuse me. It's about the job!
這是有關工作的電話
Barbara,hi! How are you?
芭芭拉,你好嗎?
No,I understand.
不,我懂
Come on. No,I'm fine. Don't be silly. Yeah.
不,我沒事,快別這麼說
But if anything else opens up,please
是否還有其他職缺請人?
Hello?
你好?
Sorry,Rach.
我很遺憾,瑞秋
There's gonna be lots of other stuff.
工作滿街都是
Okay.
好的
Where were we?
Where were we? 玩到哪兒了?
Five-card draw. Jacks are better. Nothing wild. Everybody,ante.
拿五張牌,十一點比較好,大家下注
-Look,Rach,we don't have to do this. -Yes,we do.
-瑞秋,別再玩了 -要玩,下注
-All right. Check. -Check.
-好吧,下注 -下注
-I'm in for 50 cents. -Call.
-我下5毛錢 -跟跟
I'm in.
我跟
I see your 50 cents...
我跟你5毛
...and I raise you $5.
而且我要加5塊錢
I thought it was a 50-cent limit.
我以為5毛是上限
I just lost a job, I'd like to raise it $5.
我剛失去工作所以想加5塊
Does anyone have a problem with that?
各位有問題嗎?
-Not at all. -No.
-當然沒有 -沒有
Loser?
輸家?
-No,I fold. -What do you mean,you fold?
-退出 -退出是什麼意思?怎麼了?
I thought that,"Once the cards are dealt,I'm not a nice guy."
你不是發牌後就六親不認的狠角色嗎?
Were you just full of it?
還是只是虛張聲勢?
I'm in.
我跟
-How many do you want? -One.
-幾張牌? -一張
Dealer takes two.
莊家兩張
-What do you bet? -I bet $2.
-下多少? -我下2塊
Okay. I see your $2...
我跟你2塊
...and I raise you...
再加你
... 20.
20塊
I see your $20...
我跟你20塊
... raise you $25.
再加到25塊
I see your $25 and Monica,get my purse.
跟你25塊,摩妮卡,拿我的皮包來
Rachel,there's nothing in it.
瑞秋,裡面沒錢
Okay,then get me your purse.
那就拿你的皮包來
-Here you go. Good luck! -Thank you.
-給你.祝你好運! -謝謝
I saw your $25 and I raise you...
謝謝,跟你25塊,再加
...seven.
…7塊
teen!
10塊!
Joey,I'm a little shy.
喬伊,我有點不好意思
That's okay,Ross. You can ask me.
沒問題,你有什麼問題可以問我
-What do you need? -1 5.
-要多少? -15塊
-Here's 10. -I got 5.
-這裡有10塊 -我這裡有5塊
-Thank you. -Good luck.
-謝謝 -好運氣
I am calling your 1 7.
再加十七塊
What do you got?
你拿什麼牌?
Full house.
葫蘆
You got me.
敗給你了
-That's tough to beat. -I thought we had it!
-那確實很難贏 -我因為我們會贏!
When you don't have the cards, you don't have the cards.
沒有好牌就是沒有好牌
But look how happy she is.
瞧,她多開心
-Airmail. -Airplane. Airport. Airport '75!
-航空郵件 -飛機.機場,機場75
Airport '77! Airport '79!
機場77,機場79
Time's up!
時間到
Bye Bye Birdie!
再見…小鳥
That's a bird?
那是小鳥?
That's a bird!
那就是小鳥!
Okay,it's my turn.
該我了
Go!
開始
Bean! Bean!
豆子!豆子!
The Unbearable Lightness of Being!
生命中無法承受的輕
That you get?
答對了
That you get?!
這樣就能猜中…